heavenaffiliates.com 2012-06-23

# Heaven Affiliates – Privacy Policy

As a demonstration of our commitment to protecting player privacy, we have adopted the following privacy guidelines for this website and for the gaming activity it supports.

Collection of Information: We collect, retain and use information about you only for the purpose of providing superior gaming services to you. Most of this information is supplied by you on a voluntary basis, and some is gathered automatically by our systems. We hereby undertake that in collecting your personal details, as stated in this policy, we are bound by the Data Protection Act, Chapter 440 of the Laws of Malta. We will protect your personal information and respect your privacy in accordance with best business practices and applicable laws. 

Use of Information: The information is used to protect and administer any records, accounts or data related to you; to help complete a transaction initiated by you; to comply with certain laws and regulations; to help us design and enhance our services so that we may provide you with quality services and player support; and to communicate with you about updates to our software, services, and/or website. 

Keeping Information Private: We do not distribute personal information. We do not licence, sell, rent or trade any personal information, including contact data or specific information about your accounts or other personally identifiable information, to any third party or to any other players. You have the right to access personal data held by us about you. In order to provide you with an efficient service, we and/or our service providers may require the transfer of your personal data from one country to another on world-wide basis. You hereby consent to your personal data being so transferred. 

Protection of Information: We have implemented a number of security measures to safeguard your information. It is protected on secure networks and is accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. When you access areas containing your personal player information, we use a secure server connection. Industry-standard encryption technologies are used when transferring or receiving sensitive information supplied by you. We update and test our technology on a regular basis to improve the protection of your information and to ensure the integrity of our systems. In processing of your account and associated transactions, we may have recourse to credit rating agencies, fraud detection agencies, anti-money laundering agencies and you consent to such disclosure. 

**CONSENT TO SECURITY REVIEW**

We reserve the right to conduct a security review at any time to validate your identity, age, the registration data provided by you and to verify your use of the Affiliate Network and your financial transactions for potential breach applicable law. By agreeing to the terms of our Standard Affiliate Agreement you authorise Us, Our staff, agents and suppliers to use your Personal Information and to disclose your Personal Information to third parties for the purposes of validating the information you provide to Us in the course of using the Affiliate Networks, including, where necessary, the transfer of information outside of your country. Security reviews may include but are not limited to ordering a credit report and/or otherwise verifying the information you provide against third-party databases. In addition, to facilitate these security reviews, you agree to provide such information or documentation as We may request. 

**PROTECTION OF CHILDREN**

The Affiliate Network is not intended for or directed at persons under the age of eighteen (18). Any person who provides their information to Us through any part of the Affiliate Network represents to Us that they are eighteen (18) years of age or older. It is Our policy to uncover attempts by minors to access our Affiliate Networks which may involve Us having to access and verify your Personal Information. If We become aware that a minor has attempted to or has submitted personal information via the online site, We will not accept this information and will take steps to remove such information from our records. 

**CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY**

By clicking Submit or I agree during the registration process or by your continued use of the Affiliate Network following the posting of this Privacy Policy (as applicable), you agree to this Privacy Policy. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy and will notify you of these changes by email. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy regularly.
